naturesbasket.co.in 2011-06-18

# Nature's Basket - Management

we at Nature's Basket appreciate your trust in us and our commitment to respecting and protecting the privacy of your personal information.

1\. Information collection  
2\. Using information we collect  
3\. Updating your information  
4\. Information sharing  
5\. Cookies  
6\. Protecting the privacy of children  
7\. Security & privacy  
8\. Policy changes  
9\. Links to third parties  
10\. Questions  
11\. Legal statement  
12\. Contact information

1\. Information collection

while visiting our website you may use certain services or make a purchase which will require us to collect information about you. This information could include, name, email address, mailing address, zip code, phone number, shopping preferences, pages visited, birth date, personal interests and a record of products purchased.

We may receive your information in a variety of ways including placing an order, making a purchase at our store on broadway, making a return or exchange, requesting a catalogue, receiving a gift, creating an online account, subscribing to Nature's Basket email offers & newsletters or participate in promotion or survey.

We maintain this information in a secure database. This information helps us better serve your needs while shopping. Supplying this information is entirely voluntarily by you. However if you choose not to supply certain information, some sections of our site may not be available, such as the ability to place an order, receive a promotion, or complete a survey. We also use this information to contact you if questions arise about an order you have placed.

In order to serve your needs, we may contract with companies to help us process information requests. These could include services such as, mailing houses and email service providers. These companies are in place to provide a service and protect the privacy of your information.

2\. Using information we collect

this personal information will be used internally for purposes such as placing and tracking an order, order confirmation, analysis of website use, promotional offers and catalogue distribution, customized shopping experiences, and providing other services you request. We may contact you by phone, email or postal mail concerning your order.

3\. Updating your information

we want to be in communication with you only if you would like us to be. If you would prefer not to receive catalogues or other print communications from Nature's Basket please contact us and include your exact full name, mailing address, email address and phone number. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email offers please update your email communication preferences or follow the direct link at the bottom of your email from zabars.Com. Because mailings are scheduled in advance, please allow two weeks for your email preferences to be updated and up to six to eight weeks for your communications preferences to be updated.

4\. Information sharing we have contracted with other companies to provide specialized services, such as credit card processing, name or address verification, email and catalogue distribution or promotions. These companies are contracted to respect and protect your privacy. We strive to supply you with the best gourmet experience online and in our store. At times we may combine information you have given us online, in our store or through correspondence and work with other companies to enhance your shopping experience. We may combine this information with publicly available information to further personalize and enhance your shopping experience. It is unlikely, however there is a possibility that we may disclose your personal information upon a government request, court order, or when required by law. Information will not be supplied to these agencies for marketing purposes.

5\. Cookies

cokies are small data files which are stored on your computer while visiting naturesbasket.co.in. Cookies are necessary while placing an order online. We never use cookies to store passwords, credit card numbers or other highly confidential information. We do use cookies to remember what items are in your shopping bag, identify you when you visit our site and to log you into your account pages. We may contract with other companies in order to

6\. Protecting the privacy of children

Nature's Basket & co., inc. Is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

7\. Security & privacy

we take precautionary measures and use a number of advanced security encryption tools to protect the security and accuracy of your personal information. However, no transmission over the internet is 100% secure. As a result, although we make every effort tot protect your data, we cannot guarantee or warranty the security of information you transmit to or from our web sites. Be sure to keep your password safe, do not share this information with anyone. After you place an order, or when you are ready to leave your computer especially when using a public computer terminal, be sure to log off from your account.

8\. Policy changes

occasionally we will make changes and updates to our policies. If this occurs, we will post the new policy on our website immediately. Once posted, the new policy will take immediate effect and supersede any previously stated policy.

9\. Links to third parties

we may provide links from our sites or email to other sites we think our customers may be interested in. These are provided only as a convenience. Their appearance does not imply Nature's Basket endorsement. Nature's Basket has no affiliation with these sites and those sites are operated independently, with their own security and privacy policies. We encourage you to review those policies when you visit their sites.

10\. Questions

please contact us if you have any questions after reading our privacy policy.

11\. Legal statement  
Nature's Basket Ltd. All rights reserved.

Nature's Basket® is a registered trademark of Godrej Agrovet Ltd.

All of the content on this website is subject to copyright, trademark, service mark, trade dress and other intellectual property rights or licenses held by Nature's Basket Ltd. Your use of the trademarks, service marks, trade dress and copyrighted material displayed on this website is strictly prohibited. You may download, print and store selected portions of the content, provided you (1) only use these copies of the content for your own personal, non-commercial use, (2) do not copy or post the content on any network computer or broadcast the content in any media, and (3) do not modify or alter the content in any way, or delete or change any copyright or trademark notice. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading. Nature's Basket & co., inc. Reserves complete title and full intellectual property rights in any content you download from this web site. Except as noted above, you may not copy, download, reproduce, modify, publish, distribute, transmit, transfer or create derivative works from the content. One or more patents may apply to this web site.
